Guide to the Carol Fennelly papers, 1971-1997 MS2153
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Subject files, 1977-1993; MS2153 Series 12; 5.75 Linear feet (Box 35, Box 34, Box 33, Box 32, Box 31, Box 30, Box 29, Box 28, Box 27, Box 26, Box 33A, Box 36)
  - Mitch Snyder's Death Sympathy cards, undated (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Mitch Snyder's Death Sympathy cards, undated (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Mitch Snyder's Death Sympathy cards, undated (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Mitch Snyder's Death Telegrams, 07/07/1990-07/10/1990 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Subject files, undated (Box 33)
  - Mitch Snyder Jail case, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Non-Washington community work New Brunswick, NJ, undated (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Non-Washington community work Santa Barbara, undated (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Non-Washington community work trip to Soviet Union, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Organizations: Beyond McKinney project, undated (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Organizations: Coalition for the Homeless, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Organizations: Homeless Coordinating Council, 1985-1987 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Subject files, undated (Box 33A)
  - Organizations: Homeless Coordinating Council, 1987-1990 (Box 33A, Folder 1)
  - Organizations: Jobs for Homeless People, 1988 (Box 33A, Folder 2)
  - Organizations: Lutheran Volunteer Corps, undated (Box 33A, Folder 3)
  - Organizations: North Capitol Business Association, 1993 (Box 33A, Folder 4)
  - Organizations: National Campaign to End Hunger and Homelessness in America, 1988 (Box 33A, Folder 5)
  - Organizations: National Coalition for the Homeless, undated (Box 33A, Folder 6)
  - Subject files, undated (Box 34)
  - Panhandling, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Police harassment, 1978-1981 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Policy towards homeless in D.C., 1988 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Press lists contact information, undated (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Press conference April 19 list of attendees, undated (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Protest at Vietnam Procurement Office, 07/09/1974 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Protest at Vietnam Procurement Office, 09/13/1974 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Public Service Annoucement, undated (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Services for the homeless AIDS Hospice, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Services for the homeless Association of homeless service providers, 10/28/1987 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Services for the homeless Association of Service Providers for the Homeless, undated (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Services for the homeless Directory services for homeless, 11/1988 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Services for the homeless Heath Care for the homeless program, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Services for the homeless Legal services CCNV legal clinic, undated (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Services for the homeless Medical service homeless philosophy and legal services, undated (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Services for the homeless suggested resources for information on homelessness, undated (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Statement An Alternate State of the Union, 02/1983-1990 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Statement CCNV statement, 07/15/1985 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Statement Carol Fennelly, 09/05/1991 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Statement Carol Fennelly, undated (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Statement Margaret Heckler H.H.S. Secretary, 11/04/1984 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Testimony Carol Fennelly re: Panhandling Control Act of 1991, 07/10/1991 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Testimony Mitch Snyder re: House subcommittees on Housing and Community Development and Public Buildings and Grounds, 08/01/1985 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Testimony Mitch Snyder Intergovernmental Relations and Human Resources Subcommittee of the Committee on Government Operations, 10/03/1984 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Testimony Congressional Hearings Homelessness in America [1982], undated (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Training program jobs for homeless people chef training program, undated (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Subject files, undated (Box 35)
  - Volunteers The Center for Youth Services, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Volunteers Church of the Brethren, 1980-1989 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Volunteers at FCS Shelter and MSH volunteers, undated (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Volunteers for peace "International Work Camp", 1983-1985 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Volunteers for peace "International Work Camp", 1986-1990 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Volunteers National Volunteer Clearinghouse, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Volunteers Workcamps, 1977-1985 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Voter registration for the homeless, 1984-1992 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Voter survey regarding homeless, 05/1990-06/1990 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Subject files, undated (Box 36)
  - Voter registration for the homeless, 1992-1993 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Voter registration for the homeless, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Voter registration for the homeless, undated (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Winter, 1981-1982 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Winter, 1982-1983 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Winter, 1983-1984 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Winter, 1985-1986 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Winter, 1986-1987 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Winter, 1987-1988 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Winter, 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Winter, 1991-1992 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Writings Essays, undated (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Writings by Carol Fennelly, undated (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Writings Essay by Mitch Snyder and Carol Fennelly for the book "Sharing Christmas", 1990 (Box 36, Folder 14)
- Video and audio materials, 1984-1993; MS2153 Series 13; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 39, Box 38, Box 37)
  This series contains videos, audio cassettes, and audio reel to reel tapes documenting the work of Carol Fennelly, Mitch Snyder, and the Community for Creative Non-Violence. These items date from 1984-93. The topics include homeless people, housing, and shelters.
  - Videos: AFSCME Housing Now, 10/07/1989 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    (2 vhs)
  - Videos: Housing Now "VideoEncore", undated (Box 37, Folder 2)
    (vhs)
  - Videos: Housing Now t.v. interviews, undated (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Videos: Housing Now ribbon cutting CCNV, 04/19/1989 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Videos: CCNV testimony, 04/24/1993 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Videos: Carol and CCNV Thanksgiving, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Videos: Geraldo, undated (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Videos: Fox Broadcasting company The Reporters "Shelter Boy", undated (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Videos: Classes held at homeless shelter, 05/03/1988 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Videos: City Council hearing, undated (Box 37, Folder 10)
    (beta)
  - Videos: Voices Class [Katy] Couric, undated (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Videos: Santa Barbara Citizens' action against homelessness and St. Barbara protest sleep outs in front of City Hall, 04/1990 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Videos: "2nd Street Shelter" composite tape dub, 07/1986 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Video and audio materials, undated (Box 38)
  - Videos: Carol Fennelly: Evening Exchange, undated (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Videos: "A Home for the Homeless" with Carol Fennelly and Boston Mayor Raymond Flynn, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Videos: Mitch Snyder on Night watch/CBS Charlie Rose, 02/07/1986 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Videos: Mitch Snyder on the Homeless, undated (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Videos: Mitch Snyder / Josh, undated (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Videos: CBS This Morning Dionne Warwick and Carol Fennelly interviews, 10/06/1989 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    (Umatic)
  - Videos: CBS 60 Minutes with Mitch Snyder and CCNV updated repeat presentation of edition, 11/02/1984 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Videos: Voices from the Streets, undated (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Videos: Voices from the Streets, undated (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Videos: 2nd Street Shelter and Mitch Snyder, undated (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Videos: Mitch Snyder, undated (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Videos: Mitch Snyder, 06/06/1989 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Video and audio materials, undated (Box 39)
  - Videos: CBS news, 07/1989 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Audio: Housing Now! "Song of the Homeless", undated (Box 39, Folder 2)
    (audio reel to reel)
  - Audio: Housing Now!, undated (Box 39, Folder 3)
    (audio reel)
  - Audio: Housing Now PSA with Casey Kasem, undated (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Audio: Carol Fennelly with Larry King, 12/14/1993 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    (cassette tape)
  - Audio: "Bag Lady" Blake/Begley, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - [Sher] meeting women at NIH, undated (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Oversize materials, 1986-1990; MS2153 Series 14; 1 Linear feet (Box 41, Box 40)
  This series includes posters, sketches, proclamations, and images. These items date from 1986-90.
  - Oversize materials, undated (Box 40)
  - Congressional Record "Mitch Snyder-A True American Hero", 07/11/1990 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Council of the District of Columbia Mitch Snyder Memorial Recognition Result, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Sketch of Mitch Snyder, undated (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper picture of Mitch Snyder from the Washington Post framed, undated (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Office of the Wayne County Executive Proclamation honoring Mitch Snyder (Michigan) framed, 12/09/1988 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Rosa Parks Award to the Community for Creative Non-Violence and Mitch Snyder Jacksonville Florida, 08/12/1986-08/15/1986 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Congressional Record: "Mitch Snyder- A True American Hero", 07/11/1990 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Oversize materials, undated (Box 41)
  - Commemorative framed item related to the Stewart B. McKinney Homeless Assistance Act, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Oversize images, undated (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Oversize images, undated (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - CCNV posters, undated (Box 41, Folder 4)